-[insects chirping]
-[rumbling]
[dinosaurs bellowing]
[thudding]
[roars, screeches]
[beeping]
[radar trilling]
-[beeps, pings]
-[radio static crackles]
[man on radio] Jurassic One,
Jurassic One, come in.
This is Isla Nublar Base, over.
-[woman on radio] Go, Jurassic One.
-[man] Emergency. Hostiles in pursuit.
Two friendlies in need
of immediate extraction.
-[woman] Roger that, Base! On our way.
-[velociraptors screeching]
-[rustling]
-[man panting]
We can't stop here. Follow me!
Wait. Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
[grunts]
I think we lost 'em.
-We gotta get to the chopper.
-[thuds]
[growling]
[screeches]
[velociraptor grunting]
[screeching]
Come on!
[boy grunts]
Raptor bones?
Whoa!
[man] Hurry! We're almost
to the extraction point!
[boy] No! We can use the river
to mask our scent and--
-[screams]
-[screeches]
-[man screaming]
-[boy whimpering]
[panting]
-[rumbling]
-[whimpering continues]
[growling]
-[boy] Aw, crud!
-[roars]
[menu trilling]
Dang it!
-[roars, laughs]
-[yelps]
Not cool, Brand.
Yeah, like you know what cool is.
-[keyboard clacking]
-[grunts] Get off me, Brand!
-[Brand chuckles]
-[grunts]
[chuckles] Aw, come on, man.
The dinos get you and that old dude
every time.
His name is Dr. Meriwether.
His name oughta be "Dinner."
Brand, I'm so close.
If I can just get around the T. rex,
I'd beat the game and win the--
Trip to Jurassic World.
I-I know. You've said it,
like, a thousand times.
But if straight-up gamers say
this thing's unwinnable,
how's some dino-nerd kid gonna beat it?
Great pep talk, bro.
You been working on that?
[sighs] Look, Darius, I know
getting to Jurassic World
was your and Dad's dream, but there's
more to life than just dinosaurs.
You never leave your room anymore, bruh.
Dad wouldn't want this.
I hear you, but even if winning
is dumb and hopeless,
I still gotta try, you know?
I guess so, D.
Can you at least, like, take a break?
Maybe work in a shower?
-'Cause you're smelling pretty funky, man.
-[chuckles]
[sighs] All right, look, you do you, D.
Just do it quietly.
I don't want Mom on my case again
for you staying up...
[clock ticking]
[ticking continues]
[snoring softly]
[snorts, gasps]
That's it! [yelps, grunts]
-[light clicks]
-Ah, attack patterns? No.
Vocalizations, pack behavior? No.
Got it!
So, if my theory's correct...
[trilling]
[exhales]
It's go time.
-[roars]
-[yelps]
[roars]
-[gasps]
-[thuds]
It's gotta be here somewhere.
-[roars]
-[whimpers]
[screeching]
Where are you? Where are you?
Where are you?
[gasps] There it is!
[beeps]
-[trilling]
-[screeching]
-[beeps]
-Please whistle.
-[resonating chamber whistles]
-[T. rex shrieks]
-[roars]
-[velociraptors screeching]
-[helicopter whirring]
-[gasps]
[screeching]
[roaring]
[male voice] Congratulations, player.
[controller clatters]
I'm Mr. DNA, and you're the first person
to ever beat our game,
so we wanna reward you with a trip
to Jurassic World's brand-new,
state-of-the-art adventure camp.
That's right, get ready to join us
at Camp Cretaceous!
Brand...
Mom!
[man] Welcome to Isla Nublar, campers.
You are the chosen few,
the first kids in the entire world
to ever experience the awesomeness
that is Camp Cretaceous.
I know, the trip from the mainland
was rough on some.
Hello, Ben.
[retching]
But you made it!
I'm Dave, head counselor.
You heard that correctly--
head honcho, big shot.
[tires screech]
Ah, so sorry I'm late.
Welcome, campers!
I'm Roxie, head counselor
of Camp Cretaceous.
[chuckles] Well, it's sort of
a co-head counselor sort of situation.
-Is it?
-[clears throat]
Anyway, some of you
won contests to be here,
some of you had VIP invites,
but for the next two weeks,
all of you will be getting
the five-star treatment!
As our first campers, we've lined up
exclusive behind-the-scenes tours
of Jurassic World.
-Ooh!
-Yes!
[Ben whines]
As well as kayaking, rock climbing,
obstacle courses, and of course...
Dinosaurs?
Yes... Darius, plenty of dinosaurs.
So, ready for an adventure?
Absolutely!
But I'm gonna need that speech
a little shorter,
and really try to lean
into the majesty of this place.
[chuckles] Okay, we're going now.
Let's get the six of you to camp.
Uh, there are five of us.
Wait.
Dino-kid, Track-Star, Internet Girl,
Barfy, Texas.
He's right. Where's Six?
[Roxie scoffs]
[whirring]
Greetings, my dudes.
Kenji is here, so let the party commence!
-[sputters]
-Put this in my room.
So, what's your deal? [grunts]
Okay, let's go.
[grunting]
[camera shutter clicks]
[humming]
[Kenji sighs]
[engine starts, revs]
[all scream]
[Ben] I hope you got my mom's note.
I don't do well on windy roads.
What's good, Brooklanders?
It's your girl Brooklynn coming at you
from the best place ever:
Camp Cretaceous.
Like and subscribe to join me
as I unbox Jurassic World!
Okay, I need you all to say who you are
and a little bit about yourself.
And, action!
Oh! Um...
I beat this awesome VR dinosaur game.
-I'm Darius, by the--
-I'm sorry.
I just can't believe... you're Brooklynn!
I'm Sammy Gutierrez, total Brooklander!
Kapow! [imitates gunfire]
Oh, also, my family supplies all the beef
for the park, and that's how I got here.
Great to meet you, Sammy.
Um... What's a Brooklander?
Oh, that's just what my online followers
call themselves.
Uh, all 27 million of us.
[imitates gunfire]
Yep. That's why she's the only one
who gets to keep her cell phone.
She's famous.
Hold on. Rich and famous?
Oh, meant to be.
[camera shutter clicks]
[vomiting]
[inhales, vomits]
-[tires screech]
-[all scream]
-[car door opens]
-Um, Dave, what's going on?
-Nothing you need to worry about.
-[electricity crackles]
But you should all
definitely stay in your seats.
[whimpers] Oh, God. [pants]
[whimpers] Mm.
[rustling]
Guys?
-[shrieks]
-[screams]
[all screaming]
[groans, gasps]
[clicks, roars]
[gasps]
-[roars]
-[grunts]
-[shrieking]
[Roxie] Crisis averted.
Oh, these things are always
getting out of their enclosure.
[gasps] A real live Compsognathus!
Oh, please.
It took a blanket
and a cat carrier to catch it.
Boring.
-Scared you pretty good.
-[girls laughing]
[camera shutter clicks]
[engine starts]
Whoa!
Wow.
-Whoa!
Welcome to Camp Cretaceous.
[Sammy laughing]
Oh, my gosh!
-[Brooklynn] Whoo!
-[laughs]
-[Sammy] Whoo-hoo!
-[Darius] Yeah!
-[tires screech]
-[engine turns off]
[all] Whoa!
Hey, Brooklanders, check this place out!
Is this not the most amazing place
you have ever seen?
If you think this is cool, you should see
my dad's penthouse in the main park.
Yasmina!
Hey, girl.
So, as an elite athlete,
how pumped are you for camp?
Not a huge fan of being on camera.
Or people.
This place is almost as big
as my family's ranch back home.
That's because when we're up and running,
the camp will house
500 kids and 150 staff.
Listen up!
Announcement time
from your co-head counselors.
Psst, still not a thing.
Okay, everyone,
there's some ground rules to cover.
Curfew's at 8:00 p.m.,
and lights out at 9:00 p.m. sharp.
-What?
-Lame.
Fine.
This is for your safety.
We are in a dinosaur-filled jungle.
You must always keep your distance,
or you could be seriously hurt,
if not worse.
Define "worse."
Cabins are up that-a-way.
-First one there gets top bunk!
-[Kenji grunts]
-[all laughing]
-[Sammy] Whoo-hoo!
-[shrieks]
-[Roxie] Get this lovely lady
back to her pen.
Her family's probably worried sick.
-[engine starts, revs]
-W-Wait!
Oh, man, I really wanted to get
a closer look at that Compy.
I like your enthusiasm, Darius,
but right now it's "claiming a bunk" time.
So, you know... go claim a bunk.
But it's the first dinosaur
I've ever seen in person
and, I mean, we're here
to see dinosaurs, so...
[rumbling]
Oh, the day is not over, buddy.
-Wow!
-[dinosaurs bellowing]
Dinosaurs!
[Darius laughs] There's Brachiosaurus.
Parasaurolophus. Stegosaurus.
Ankylosaurus!
Wow, you really do know
your stuff, dino-nerd.
Check out the... Brontosaurus.
They don't have those here.
Common mistake.
[Darius gasps] Are those Sinoceratops?
When did you get those?
They are cooking up
all kinds of new dinos in that lab.
Whoa! Where are they herding 'em to?
They're herding them back
to their nighttime enclosures.
Enough banter.
It's zip-line party time!
Me? Maybe Yasmina
should go first, or... Darius?
Uh... Or anyone! I really don't--
[screams]
[all laughing, cheering]
[dinosaurs bellowing]
Wow!
Whoa! [screams]
Whoa!
[cheering continues]
-[Yasmina] Yeah!
-[Kenji cackling]
[snoring]
-[light clicks]
-[Darius gasps]
Oh, hey there, dino-nerd. Whatcha doing?
Huh? Uh, nothing!
I was just, uh, heading out 'cause...
thirsty.
Oh, yeah. I... I meant, um... hungry.
Oh, heh, look at that. Thanks, Kenji.
Look, bro.
I don't want you to be intimidated by me
just because I'm rich,
my father owns a few condos
on the island, and I'm rich.
-Uh, I'm not intimidated by you.
-Oh, good.
I just want us to be friends,
and friends tell each other stuff.
For instance, what they're doing
out of bed after curfew.
What do you think?
I think you best get your arm
off me... friend.
Oh. Why don't you make me, friend?
-[camera shutter clicks]
-[Brooklynn] Huh.
So that's what toxic masculinity
looks like.
Uh, sorry we woke you. I--
He was sneaking out,
but I set him straight.
Look, I try to look out
for the younger kids.
It's who I am.
[Darius] You guys don't understand.
I've been waiting my whole life
to get here,
and I'm gonna make the most of it.
Those lights must be coming
from the Compy enclosure.
I gotta check it out!
Sneaking out to see dinosaurs
in the dead of night,
mad danger of getting caught,
great mood lighting... [sighs]
I guess that means...
we're going rogue.
Kapow!
I think this is it.
The truck definitely headed
this direction.
Of course this is it.
Why else would they have--
[engine starts]
Shh!
[Kenji] Hey, Brooklynn.
You can get a good shot from over here.
-Allow me.
-No, thanks. I can--
-Just-- [grunts]
-Hey!
[Brooklynn] Give me my-- Ugh!
Come on! [gasps]
[bangs, clatters]
Thanks, Kenji. Real smooth.
Relax, I'll get it.
-Wait! What are you--
-I got it, kid.
[grunts]
See? Ha! Good as new.
Great. Now, just climb back up
and gently hand it to me.
Sure, sure, right after I get
a sweet dino-pic for your followers.
No need to thank me.
-[rustling]
-[gasps]
Um, guys...
this isn't the Compy pen.
Quiet, junior!
The grown-ups are talking.
Ah, your followers are gonna love this.
Here, Compy-Compy-Compy.
This isn't the Compy pen!
-Uh, what's he babbling on about?
-[growling]
What the...?
[snarls]
-[camera shutter clicks]
-[screeches]
[screams]
-[roars]
-[screaming]
[Brooklynn] Come on!
-[Kenji pants]
-[grunting]
-[panting]
-[screeches]
-[velociraptor snarling]
D'ah! Open the gate! Open the gate!
[Kenji whimpers]
-[alarm blaring]
-Oh, please! Let me out! [screams]
[grunting] Oh, come on!
-D'ah!
-[snarls]
[hisses]
-[thudding]
-[whimpers]
[grunting]
[steam hissing]
Dude! Please tell me you have a plan.
Let's move!
The steam should keep him busy.
Huh?
[blaring continues]
[screeching]
Oh, crud!
[theme music playing]